# Yining (Winnie) Wu

2/13 Hadlow Drive WANTIRNA VIC 3152 Mobile: 0435275166

E-mail: wyndwz@gmail.com

## **Summary**

I am currently working as a web developer in both Allori and Beddoes Institute. With strong skills of Ruby on Rails backend development, I also have experience in frontend development with rails framework (like Bootstrap). From my work, I was involved in commercial projects (like Tess) which will be introduced in my Project Experience section. In addition, I am also familiar with survey tools like LimeSurvey, developing customized thems with JavaScript and CSS and building client surveys in complex logic. Volunteer experience working on image processing and mining big data. Internship working on web front and back end development. Strong ability of team work, time management skills and communication skills. I am always excited to learn new technology and work efficiently in my positions.

## **Employment**

Nov 2018 – Present Allori(https://www.allori.com.au/)

**Beddoes Institute** 

(https://www.beddoesinstitute.com.au/)

Web Developer – Full time Melbourne, VIC Australia

#### **Education**

Master of Computer Science GPA: 5.438

University of Adelaide

2016 Adelaide, South Australia

Bachelor of Computer Science and Technology
East China University of Political Science and Law

2014 Shanghai, Shanghai China

# **Project Experience**

Tess (Beddoes Institute) Dec 2018 - Releasing and Ongoing

Project URL: <a href="https://tess.beddoes.com.au/">https://tess.beddoes.com.au/</a>

Tess is a comprehensive platform collecting and analysing data of financial advisers around Australia. The system collects data of advisers' detail from client companies (e.g. AIA, AMP etc.), ASIC government and website scraping. Also, revenues for each adviser and business are collected in the system.

 Core Function Development: Responsible for entire workflow with both frontend and backend development. Create auto-algorithm to build relationship with multiple tables.

- Reliability Assurance: Monitoring weekly update crone jobs in order to get latest data into database.
- Quality Assurance: Build unit tests and design test case for validation of the code quality. (Capybara)
- Server maintenance: Set up server and ensure app running smoothly, CI/CD.

Skills: Ruby on rails, CSS, HAML, HTML, JavaScript (JQuery), SASS, MySQL, Bootstrap

#### Claims Data Dashboard (Beddoes Institute) May 2019 - Jun 2020

Claims Data Dashboard App is a tool for data analysis using Hightcharts. The data is collected from survey results using backend Limesurvey API connection. Create different filters for customers to analyse the results and the current trend of different types of insurance from various companies.

- Core Function Development: Responsible for entire workflow with both frontend and backend development. Mainly focus on data management and frontend development.
- Quality Assurance: Build unit tests and design test case for validation of the code quality.
   (Capybara)
- Server Maintenance: Set up server and ensure app running smoothly, CI/CD.
- Project Merging: Responsible for merging the project into Tess. Fix conflicts and frontend style consistency.

Skills: Ruby on rails, CSS, HAML, HTML, JavaScript (JQuery), SASS, MySQL, Highcharts

#### Limesurvey Development (Beddoes Institute) Apr 2019 - Releasing and Ongoing

Create commercial surveys using Limesurvey. Focus on frontend and plugin development.

- Core Function Development: Responsible for survey frontend and logic development.
- Quality Assurance: Build auto tests and design test case for logic of the survey(Capybara).
- Server Maintenance: Set up server and ensure app running smoothly.
- Plugin development: Build simple plugin to create questions with complex logic.

Skills: CSS, HTML, JavaScript (JQuery), PHP, MySQL, Limesurvey API.

#### **Volunteer Work**

September 2016 to January 2017

Volunteer in YourAmigo, Adelaide

Completed the project which recognized the face position of people in images with python. Gained skills in following areas:

- Image processing with OpenCV
- Machine leaning in facial recognition
- Feature extraction
- Python language

Completed some random works related to website development including front end and back end.

- Basic understanding of process maker
- User Interface development for mobile application
- Usability audit for website
- Improvement of documentation skills
- Javascrip, CSS, HTML, Ratchet

### **Degree Related Projects**

My master project is investigating the use of wearables for monitoring post-operative children in hospitals. The aim is to monitor post-operative children in hospitals and evaluate recovery time after surgery with wearable devices. There are 2 PHD students, a professor and a doctor in hospital assisting me with this project. The following details describe the approach:

- Explore the use of wearable sensors (accelerometer, gyroscope, air pressure, skin temperature and heart rate) with young children
- Collect physiological and movement data in real time with database
- Build classification (Support vector machine with different kernels) models to recognize activities of children in real time

I also conducted experiments in the Women and Children Hospital in Adelaide. The system was built as follows: -

- Access sensors on Microsoft band 2
- A mobile phone is used to label ground truth in real time

The results I have obtained are promising. However, the accuracy of the classification in my project only reached around 50% due to the sensor data from children which are not so direct. After that, our team published a research paper in a conference (EasyChair) named 'Can one smart watch capture child activities? A benchmark to monitor level of activities in post-operative children.'

### **Technical Skills**

Advanced: Java, Python, Ruby

Languages: JavaScript, Matlab, PHP, CSS, HTML, Jquery, SASS

Applications: Eclipse, Matlab, Android Studio, Sensor data collection

**Operating Systems:** Windows, Linux, MacOS, Canva, Blogger, Vimeo, Google Slides, Flip Grid, LinkedIn, Survey Monkey

**Frameworks and tools:** Ruby on Rails, Boostrap, Version control tool (such as Git), Test Driven Development (such as Capybara), Highcharts

Database Systems: MySQL, PostgreSQL

# **Soft Skills**

- Good communication, team work and interpersonal skills
- Strong strategic planning skills, analytical skills and time management skills
- Good building business relationships skills
- good attention to detail and OHS&W skills

# Languages

Chinese - Native English - Fluent

# **Awarded Diplomas**

ACS Professional Year Program

Certificate IV in Business

Advanced Diploma of Translating

### Referees

Available if required.